Music
Good morning!
I'm going to Osaka for the first time.
Tired, me and Shinka.
And the other members.
I'll be there!
I just bought an ekiben.
I'm going to eat it on the Shinkansen.
Do ekiben!
Good morning!
The first one!
the first
It's my first ekiben!
Good morning.
To Chris
Good morning
Yay!
This one.
I'm torn between two right now.
I've decided.
Boo-bahn.
I'm out!
Oh, Sminer.
Ments la
Boo-boo!
I did it!
It's so fresh!
I've got nine minutes left, and if I don't drink more and more, I'll never make it in time.
I'm gonna go a little fast.
What's going on?
Just give me a second.
I can't find my phone.
Wait a minute.
No pass.
No phone.
I put it in here.
Yay, yay, yay.
Oh, my God. You scared the shit out of me.
I left you on the train.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
I took a night camera.
I got it!
Let's go to the next event!
Let's go!
This is the bento recommended by Mr. Amifrasi!
I'm going to enjoy it with everyone else.
Let's go!
We're just getting started! I'll do my best!
Well then, Mie, shall I fix your back?
Mie, I feel like I'm in the sky.
I feel like I'm in the sky.
Oh!
Is it hurting too much?
Oh, that looks painful.
I can't even think about it.
I won't say it.
I don't
Ç
Nice to meet you all, let's have fun together today!
Quick, take the dark, Weir, Earthburger
Rings a bell, rings a bell
Let's end on a high note with this song!
Summerleaves
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you so much for giving us a fancier experience!
I'm so excited! It's like...
Oh my god! I'm so excited!
And Mercy, who is putting on this event And Mercy, who is putting on this event
This is a joint event with PTG of the same generation.
I have a plan for this event.
Seino
Let's go!
Ready go!
Yes!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Start.
Penguin.
Berry Berry-Go-Round
Amazing
Proposal
Yes.
I'm serious.
Yay!
Applause
Clap
Anstoports
Correct answer
Stop.
Angst Ports.
It was our first trip to Osaka.
We had a lot of new customers.
I was so happy to see so many new customers.
Some of them said they would come to our one-man show.
That's a nod.
A nod. Thank you very much.
We're looking forward to seeing you.
It was a lot of fun.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Today's fortune is goo. Today's fortune is a goo
So I'll go with “goo”.
Today's fortune is “P.” Then I'll go with “P.
Today's fortune for me is...
Suit.
Jaboo.
Nice.
I'll get it.
Look at this place
Hidbeth
Expo girl
I'm really curious